

PEDRO GABRIEL CAIRES

Fullstack Web Developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Hello world! My name is Pedro Gabriel and I'm a Fullstack dev with specialization in PHP/Laravel

MY STORY

I started programming when I was 16, I've always been a hardware and software lover, when I started to attend the Technician School in Computer Science it was a big definitive push into the area. In 2020, along with two long time friends, I created Phog Tech, a freelance team specialized in Web solutions. After that I participated in several Open Source projects and now I currently work at I'M Labs, a company of diverse technological solutions. I stand out for my agility with new technologies and the ease of solving problems.

SKILLS

- PHP (Laravel, Lumen, Symphony & others)Javascript (Node.js, Vue.js, React.js)
- MySQL (and other relational databases)
 - Python
 - Java
 - React Native
 - Docker
 - AWS (and other cloud solutions)
 - Intermediate English

EDUCATION

- "Curso Técnico em Informática" at Eniac College (2019~2021)
- College in Information Systems at FIAP (2022~Present)

CONTACT

Cell Phone: +55 11 986341150 Email: pedrogcs0104@gmail.com

LINKS

GITHUB: https://github.com/dgtyPedro

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-gabriel-caires/

EXPERIENCE

PHOG TECH

PHP Back-End Developer (2020~2021)

I was responsible for structuring and developing all database part of the projects that the team was hired. During this period I learned a lot about PHP as a language itself and how MySQL databases worked.

I'M LABS

Fullstack Developer (2021~Present)

An excellent opportunity in which I was exposed to several new and different technologies, I could test a little bit of everything and it was the period that I am learning the most in my life. I made several projects with ViteJs, Next, Laravel/Jetstream and other technologies. In the last few months I have been working mostly with Laravel, which has become my main technology.

NOTABLE PROJECTS

- Lotopower: Lottery tips and simulations platform, made 100% by me in Laravel. LINK: https://lotopower.com.br

- **dumpi-fy**: Spotify playlist manager made in PHP.

LINK: https://github.com/dgtyPedro/dumpi-fy

- **Geek Horror:** Horror Quizz site, I did the backend in PHP.

LINK: https://geekhorror.com.br

- AdaWendy: SPA made 100% by me in React for the company AdaWendy.

LINK: https://www.adawendy.com.br